Guide to the Progressive Cities and Neighborhood Planning 1969-2005 Collection, 1969-2005
Progressive Cities and Neighborhood Planning 1969-2005 Collection, 1969-2005
- Series II. Great Britain
  - Other Articles
    - "Municipal Enterprise and Popular Planning." New Left Review. 159: p. 117-124., Sept.-Oct. 1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      3 copies. Photocopy. 3 pages. -- Author: Palmer, John.
    - "Sharing the Caring." New Statesman. p. 8-10., Jan. 13, 1984. (Box 5, Folder 3)
      3 copies. Photocopy. 3 pages. -- Author: Rowbotham, Sheila.
    - "Lessons of the London Industrial Strategy." New Left Review. p. 75-84., Jan.-Feb. 1986. (Box 5, Folder 4)
      4 copies. Photocopy. 7 pages. -- Author: Rustin, Michael.
    - City of Sheffield, Sheffield City Council - Positive Action Project. Positive Action for Women Project: Final Report., Oct. 22, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      2 copies. Photocopy. 75 pages.
    - City of Sheffield, Sheffield City Council. Sheffield Music Factory: Final Report. Municipal Music Services: Support for the Music Economy and the Unemployed in Sheffield., July 1, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      2 copies. Photocopy. 24 pages.
    - City of Sheffield, Sheffield City Council. An Agreement between the Sheffield City Council and the Sheffield Urban Development Corporation., Aug. 19, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      2 copies. Photocopy. 4 pages.
    - City of Sheffield, Sheffield City Council. The Role of the Business Community., Nov. 18, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      2 copies. Photocopy. 3 pages.
    - City of Sheffield, Employment Department. Checklist of Work in Progress., June 1, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      2 copies. Photocopy.14 pages.
    - City of Sheffield, Employment Department. A Guide to the Department., June 8, 1905 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - City of Sheffield, Employment Programme Committee. Outlook Report 1990-93., July 23, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      3 copies. Photocopy. 11 pages.
    - City of Sheffield, Employment Department. Review of the Work in the First Year 1982-83., June 1, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      2 copies. Photocopy. 46 pages.
    - City of Sheffield. Department of Land and Planning, Planning Division, Employment Department. Report to Employment Programme Committee., Dec. 3, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      2 copies. Photocopy. 13 pages.
    - "The Socialist Republic of South Yorkshire." Critical Social Policy. p. 72-93. (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - "Labour and the local state in Liverpool." Capital & Class. (Box 5, Folder 15)
      Photocopy. 3 pages. -- Author: Thompson, Paul and Mike Allen.
    - "London after Abolition." Local Government Studies. p. 105-116, May/June 1990 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      Photocopy. 5 pages. -- Author: Travers, Tony.
    - "Walsall's Haul to Democracy: The Neighborhood Concept." & Notes on the Neighborhood Concept. (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Original Bound Publication and Handwritten Notes. 30 pages. -- Author: Powell, Brian.
    - "Labour's Capital Gains: The GLC Experience." Marxism Today. p. 24-29., Dec. 1, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      2 copies. Photocopy. 5 pages. -- Author: Ward, Michael.
    - After redundancy: A study of some responses to unemployment in the Sheffield steel industry., Dec. 1, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      2 copies. Photocopy. 7 pages. -- Author: Westergaard, John and Alan Walker.
  - Collection of Issues of Campaign. Produced by Economic Development Committee, West Midlands County Council. Multiple Issues., 1984-85
    - Issue 3., July 1984. (Box 5, Folder 20)
      Original Newsprint. 4 pages.
    - Issue 4., Sept. 1984. (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Issue 5., Nov. 1984. (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Issue 6., Feb. 1985. (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Issue 7., Apr. 1985. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - West Midlands County Council. Economic Development Committee: Campaign For Jobs Publications
    - West Midlands County Council. Jobs at Risk. (Box 5, Folder 21)
      Original Publication. 25 pages.
    - Priorities for Economic Regeneration I the West Midlands. Paper presented to the County Economic Development Committee in November 1981., Nov. 1, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      Original Bound Publication. 5 pages -- Author: Edge, Geoff.
    - West Midlands County Council. Directory of Worker Co-operatives. (Box 5, Folder 23)
      Original Bound Publication. 63 pages.
    - Regional Industrial Development: Assisted Area Designation Criteria and Boundaries. Supplementary Response of the County Council of West Midlands., May 1, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - The West Midlands: What can it offer your Business? West Midlands County Council, Economic Development Committee. Prepared by the Economic Development Committee: Campaign For Jobs, West Midlands County Council. (Box 5, Folder 25)
      Original Bound Publication. 17 pages.
    - "West Midlands Campaign For Jobs: It's Working." Advertisement Extra, West Midlands County Council., Nov. 1, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      3 copies. Original Newsprint. 4 pages.
    - Research Paper No. 1: Women in the West Midlands Economy., June 1984. (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Research Paper No. 6: Resources for Economic Development., July 1985. (Box 5, Folder 27)
      Original Bound Publication. 27 pages
    - Economic Review: Combating Industrial Decline. No. 1., May 1, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      Original Bound Publication. 33 pages.
    - Economic Review: Tackling Poverty. No. 2., Aug. 1984. (Box 5, Folder 27)
      Original Bound Publication. 45 pages.
    - Economic Review: Jobs and Technology. No. 3., Feb. 1985. (Box 5, Folder 27)
      Original Bound Publication. 53 pages.
    - Unemployment Briefing. December 1985 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - West Midlands Enterprise Board Publications, 1983-1988
    - Enterprise. Issue 2. West Midlands Enterprise Board., Jan. 1986. (Box 5, Folder 28)
      Original Publication. 2 pages.
    - Enterprise. Issue 4. West Midlands Enterprise Board., Sept. 1986. (Box 5, Folder 28)
      2 copies. Original Publication. 3 pages.
    - Enterprise. Issue 5. West Midlands Enterprise Board., Dec. 1986. (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Enterprise. Issue 6. West Midlands Enterprise Board., Mar. 1988. (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Enterprise. Issue 10. West Midlands Enterprise Board., Mar. 1988. (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Report and Financial Statements 1985. West Midlands Enterprise Board LTD., Aug. 30, 1985. (Box 5, Folder 28)
      Original Publication. 20 pages.
    - Risk Capital for Developing Business in the West Midlands Region. (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Local knowledge and local finance to help West Midlands business develop and flourish. (Box 5, Folder 28)
      Photocopy. 10 pages.
    - The West Midlands Enterprise Board Second Fund: A Proposal., Apr. 25, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Purpose, Policy and Procedures., Apr. 29, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 28)
      Photocopy. 17 pages.
  - West Midlands Sector Research Publications, 1985
    - Bibliography. (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - University of Warwick Science Park Brochure. (Box 5, Folder 29)
      Original Publication. 7 pages.
    - Audio Visual Media in the West Midlands. A Report to the West Midlands County Council Economic Development Committee, 1985., June 7, 1905 (Box 5, Folder 29)
      Original Publication. 21 pages.
    - Interest Relief Scheme for Capital Investment. West Midlands County Council and ICFC. (Box 5, Folder 29)
      Original Pamphlet Publication. 3 pages.
    - New Enterprise Workshops: A Place to Start Your Own Business. (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Publications List. University of Birmingham Joint Centre for Regional, Urban and Local Government Studies., Oct. 1985 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      Original Bound Publication. 54 pages.
    - Re-structuring the Regions. Birmingham: Center for Urban and Regional Studies, University of Birmingham. Occasional Paper #11., June 1984 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      Original Bound Publication.48 pages. -- Author: Wray, Ian.
  - City of Sheffield, Economic Development Department. Internal Documents and Documents pertaining to ED strategies.
    - Aids to Enterprises: Review and Proposed Strategy. (Box 5, Folder 32)
      Photocopy. 16 pages.
    - Report 22.7.82: Interim Appraisal Criteria. (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Industrial Investment., Apr. 20, 1982. (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Report to E.P.C. - New Technology and Product Development Panel. The Development of Innovation and Technology Resources in Sheffield., Nov. 19, 1984. (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Report to The Training and Development Panel of the Personnel Services Sub-Committee (Policy). Sheffield Apprenticeship Training Project., Nov. 9, 1984. (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - "Higher Rates Do Not Mean Higher Unemployment." Municipal Journal., Feb. 24, 1984. (Box 5, Folder 32)
      Photocopy. 2pages. -- Author: Cowan, Michael.
    - Departmental Review. (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - A Three Year Resource Plan to Meet Changing Needs., Sept. 26, 1984. (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Review of Policy and Budget Process. Joint Report of City Treasurer and Director of Environmental Health. (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Employment Department: An Initial Outline. (Box 5, Folder 32)
      Photocopy. 8 pages.
    - Employment and Unemployment. (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - "Review of the Employment Department's Work in the Pilot Phase and Plans and Priorities for the Next Year." Editorial Group Meeting., Apr. 25, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Review of Council's Organisation and Management., May 4, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 32)
      Photocopy. 9 pages. -- Author: Benington, John.
    - Economic Development, Enforced Competition and Subsequent Matters - Departmental Responsibilities., Oct., 1987. (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Green Community Project., June 6, 1905 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Departmental Meeting., Dec. 17, 1982. (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - New Socialist Articles on Rate-Capping.
    - "The Phony." July 1985. (Box 5, Folder 33)
      Photocopy. 4 pages. -- Author: Lansley, Stewart.
    - "Thatcher to Liverpool: Drop Dead." November 1985. (Box 5, Folder 33)
      Photocopy. 4 pages. -- Author: Jones, Mervyn.
    - "Divided we Stand." December 1984. (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - "On The Brink." April 1985. (Box 5, Folder 33)
      Photocopy. 2 pages. -- Author: Blunkett, David.
    - "Local Socialists at Sticking Point." March 1985. (Box 5, Folder 33)
      Photocopy. 3 pages. -- Author: Gyford, John.
    - "The New Urban Left: A Local Road to Socialism?" April 1983. (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Local Government in Britain and Germany. Birmingham: University of Birmingham, Anglo-German Foundation for the study of Industrial Society., 1995 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    Original Bound Publication. 123 pages. -- Author: Norton, Alan
  - Binder of Women's Issues and Publications in the UK. (Box 5)
    - GLC Women's Committee. Programme of Action for Women in London., June 6, 1905 (Box 5)
      Copy in Compiled Loose-leaf Binder. 47 pages.
    - West Midlands Count Council, Economic Development Unit. Research Paper No. 1: Women in West Midlands Economy., June 1, 1984 (Box 5)
      Copy in Compiled Loose-leaf Binder. 17 pages.
    - Greater London Council. London Against Racism. (Box 5)
      Copy in Compiled Loose-leaf Binder. 5 pages.
    - Greater London Council. Changing the World: A London Charter for GAY and LESBIAN Rights. (Box 5)
      Copy in Compiled Loose-leaf Binder. 46 pages.
  - UK - Not Bennington stuff
    - Adult Education and Training for Local Economic Development. Discussion Paper Prepared for Great Lakes Economic Development Group Conference on Responses to Economic Restructuring, September 26-28, 1990. Chicago, IL., Aug. 1, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      Author: Mayo, Marjorie.
    - Training and Employment Research Unit: A Guide to Activities and Staff. Glasglow., Mar. 1, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      Author: McGregor, Alan.
    - Public-Private Co-operation in West Central Scotland. Paper prepared for the Great Lakes Economic Development Group Conference o Responses to Economic Restructuring: University of Illinois at Chicago, Chicago, IL., Sept. 1, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      Author: Lever, William.
    - A Tale of Two Cities: Revitalizing Corby, Northamptonshire and Youngstown, Ohio. Forthcoming in Peter B. Meyer (ed.), Comparative Studies in Local Economic Development, Greenwood Press, 1991., Aug. 28, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      Author: Buss, Terry F.
    - Local Work: Monthly Bulletin of the Centre for Local Economic Strategies. No. 16., Apr./May, 1990. (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Local Work: Monthly Bulletin of the Centre for Local Economic Strategies. No. 19., Aug. 1, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Local Work: Monthly Bulletin of the Centre for Local Economic Strategies. No. 20., Sept., 1990. (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - European Research Network. Consultancy Brochure. (Box 5, Folder 35)
      Original. 8 pages.
    - Center for Local Economic Strategies Brochure. (Box 5, Folder 35)
      2 copies. Original. 2 pages.
    - Love's Labor Lost: Progressive Planning in Chicago and Sheffield., Mar. 1988. (Box 5, Folder 35)
      Typescript. 25 pages. -- Author: Clavel, Pierre and Robert Kraushaar.
    - Braunstone Employment Project. Strategy Document (June 1982) and Annual Report, 1989-1990 with Personal Letter dated November 7, 1990 to Pierre Clavel: From Shanie Lee, Project Manager. (Box 5, Folder 35)
      Photocopy. 28 pages -- Author: Lee, Shanie
    - The Braunstone Experience. Program for the National Conference: Neighbourhood Economic Development., Mar. 12, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Program for the Empowering Communities Conference at Ruskin College, Oxford, UK. Community Development Journal., Nov. 2, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - London Borough of Wandsworth. Prosperity or Slump? The future of Wandsworth's economy. A Report of the Policy Review Sub-committee., Oct. 1976. (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Waterfront redevelopment, economic restructuring and social impact. (Box 5, Folder 35)
      Author: Tweedale, Iain.
    - "Epilogue: The Future of Social Policy in the United States: Political Constraints and Possibilities." in The Politics of Social Policy in the U.S. Princeton University Press, p. 423-445., June 10, 1905 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      Author: Weir, Margaret, Ann Shola Orloff and Theda Skocpol.
    - "Dismantling Flexibility." Capitol and Class. 34: 42-75., Spring 1988 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      Author: Pollert, Anna.
    - Great Lakes Economic Development Conference. List of Participants. (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - "Urban Redevelopment, Compulsory Purchase, and the Regeneration of Local Economies: The Case of Cardiff Docklands." Planning Practice and Research. 4 (3): 18-27., Winter 1989 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      Author: Thomas, Huw and Rob Imrie.
    - "Struggles in the Welfare State: A Parable of How Things Might be Done Differently" Critical Social Policy, p. 69-87. (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - The London Strategic Policy Committee. London Strategic Policy Unit. (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - "Community Action Programmes in the Early Eighties - What Future? Critical Social Policy, p. 5-17. (Box 5, Folder 35)
      Author: Mayo, Marg.
    - "Struggles in the Welfare State: Propaganda by Examples: The economic policies of the Greater London Council." Critical Social Policy, p. 64-71. (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Leeds, UK
    - "Workers' Plan: An Alternative to Entrepreneurialism?" International Journal of Urban and Regional Research Volume 8, No. 3, p. 421-437., June 6, 1905 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Original Bound Publication. 9 pages. -- Author: Cooke, Philip.
    - Leeds Urban Audit Bulletin. No. 3., Sept., 1988. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Original Bound Publication. 14 pages.
    - Leeds Urban Audit Bulletin. No. 4., Feb., 1989. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Leeds Polytechnic, Policy Research Unit. Research and Consultancy. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Original Bound Publication. 6 pages.
    - Towards a Local Labour Market Strategy. Leeds Polytechnic, Policy Research Unit., Aug., 1989. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Original Bound Publication. 9 pages. -- Author: Campbell, Michael.
    - Leeds Polytechnic, Policy Research Unit. The Wakefield Employment Skills Survey. Volume 1: Main Report., Mar., 1989. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Original Bound Publication. 67 pages.
    - Leeds City Policy Review Position Statement. Leeds Polytechnic, Policy Research Unit., July 1, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Original Bound Publication. 100 pages. -- Author: Campbell, Michael and Ian Sandeson.
    - Leeds City Council's Housing Service: A Survey of Tenants' Attitudes. Leeds Polytechnic, Policy Research Unit., May, 1989. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Original Bound Publication. 124 pages. -- Author: Brady, Sean, Mike Campbell, Janie Percy-Smith, and Brendan Sheehan.
    - "Policy Review Section." Regional Studies. Vol. 22, 1, pp. 55-68. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Original Bound Publication. 13 pages. -- Author: Mawson, J.
    - Charter for Jobs: Economic Report. London, UK. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Original Bound Publication. 13 pages. -- Author: Shields, Jon and Mark Cornelius.
    - "Jobs Blitz Aims at the Destruction of North-South Divide." Financial Guardian., Sept. 17, 1987. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Campbell, Michael.
    - Economic Sense: Local Jobs Plans. The Distribution of Jobs by Local Authority. Leeds Polytechnic, Policy Research Unit. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Photocopy. 20 pages. -- Author: Campbell, Michael, Mike Hardy, Nige Healey, Richard Stead, John Sutherland.
    - Social Audit Network News. Issue No. 1., May, 1989. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Original Bound Publication. 10 pages.
    - Center for Local Economic Strategies, Research Study Series. Meeting Real Needs - Creating Real Jobs., Nov. 1, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Original Bound Publication. 121 pages.
  - Greater London Council. London Facts and Figures., Nov. 1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Original Bound Publication. 20 pages.
  - Greater London Council. Many Happy Returns: 95 Years of Working for London., Sept. 1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Original Bound Publication. 28 pages.
  - Greater London Enterprise Board. More Than Bricks and Mortar: Making Property Work For People. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    3 copies. Original Publication and Copies. 46 pages.
  - Greater London Enterprise Board. Organising for Equality. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Partnership in Urban Regeneration and Local Economic Development: The Case Study of Sheffield: UK., Sept. 1990 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    3 copies. Photocopy. 15 pages. -- Author: Lawless, Paul.
  - Cities in Cloudless Air: Progressive Planning in Sheffield, England. Prepared for the ACSP Conference, Buffalo NY, October 1988., Oct. 1988 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    2 copies. Photocopy. 29 pages. -- Author: Kraushaar, Robert.
  - Greater London Council. Homelessness in London. Housing and Research and Policy Report - 1., Aug. 1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    2 copies. Original Bound Publication. 32 pages.
  - Southwark Women's Equality Unit. How to Keep Your Accounts: A Guide for Women's Groups., 1985 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Original Bound Publication. 19 pages.
  - Greater London Council. London Against Racism. (Box 6, Folder 10)
    3 copies. Original Publication and Copies. 9 pages.
  - "Goodbye GLC." New Socialist. Interview with Sheila Rowbotham and Hilary Wainwright., Apr. 1986 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Photocopy. 3 pages. -- Author: Livingstone, Ken.
  - "Renaissance Labour Style." Marxism Today. p. 19-27., Dec. 1984 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    4 copies. Photocopy. 8 pages. -- Author: Livingstone, Ken.
  - Greater London Council Women's Committee Publications.
    - Women and Employment. Report No. W574., June 6, 1905 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Original Publication. 12 pages.
    - Women on the Move. GLC Survey on Women and Transport., June 7, 1905 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Original Publication. 16 pages.
    - Women, Jobs and the GLC: Working out the Future. (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Original Publication. 28 pages.
    - "Job Sharing and How To Do It." Equity Information. (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Original Publication. 5 pages.
    - GLC Women's Committee. Issue 20. (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Original Publication. 60 pages.
    - GLC Women's Committee. Issue 23., Mar., 1985. (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Original Publication. 68 pages.
    - GLC Women's Committee. Issue 24., July, 1985. (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Original Publication. 56 pages.
    - Information Pack. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Greater London Council Women's Committee. Programme of Action for Women in London., 1984 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    3 copies. Original Publication and Copies. 83 pages.
  - Sheffield - A Case Study in Economic Regeneration., Sept. 1990 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    3 copies. Photocopy. 4 pages. -- Author: Hayman, Keith.
  - The New Municipal Socialism., Dec. 17, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Photocopy. 29 pages. -- Author: Green, Geoff.
  - Greater London Regional Council of the Labour Party. GLC Election 1981. Report of the Industry and Employment Working Party. (Box 6, Folder 17)
    3 copies. Photocopy. 27 pages.
  - "A New Look at Regional Planning." Town & County Planning. p. 14-15., Jan. 1983 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Photocopy. 2 pages. -- Author: Mawson, John, and David Miller.
  - Maps of Sheffield, 1988
    - Road Network and Landmarks. (Box 6, Folder 19)
      3 copies. Photocopy. 1 page.
    - Economic Development Map. Sheffield Development Office. Autumn 1988. (Box 6, Folder 19)
      Original Publication. 4 pages.
  - London Industrial Strategy Series.
    - Introduction. (Box 6, Folder 20)
      Original Bound Publication. 64 pages.
    - Summary. (Box 6, Folder 20)
      Original Bound Publication. 77 pages.
    - Arms Conversion (Box 6, Folder 20)
      Original Bound Publication. 36 pages.
    - Cable (Box 6, Folder 20)
      2 copies. Original Bound Publication. 29 pages.
    - Cleaning (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - The Clothing Industry (Box 6, Folder 20)
      Original Bound Publication. 31 pages.
    - Computer Software (Box 6, Folder 20)
      Original Bound Publication. 27 pages.
    - Construction (Box 6, Folder 20)
      Original Bound Publication. 52 pages.
    - The Cultural Industries (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - The Docks (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Domestic Work and Childcare (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Energy (Box 6, Folder 20)
      Original Bound Publication. 30 pages.
    - The Food Industry (Box 6, Folder 20)
      Original Bound Publication. 38 pages.
    - The Furniture Industry (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Healthcare (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Heathrow and West London (Box 6, Folder 20)
      2 copies. Original Bound Publication. 27 pages.
    - Instrument Engineering (Box 6, Folder 20)
      2 copies. Original Bound Publication. 21 pages.
    - The Printing Industry (Box 6, Folder 20)
      Original Bound Publication. 40 pages.
    - Public Transportation (Box 6, Folder 20)
      Original Bound Publication. 39 pages.
    - Retailing (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - The Tourism Industries. (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Greater London Council. Planning for The Future of London: The Greater London Development Plan. (includes maps), Sept. 1984 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Original Bound Publication. 237 pages.
  - "A Socialist GLC in Capitalist Britain?" Capital & Class. p. 116-133., Winter 1982 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    3 copies. Photocopy. 10 pages.
  - Greater London Council Economic Policy Group's Popular Planning Unit. Jobs for a Change., 1983 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    Original Bound Publication. 72 pages.
  - "Ownership, Control and the Market." New Left Review. Vol. 164, p. 87-112., July/Aug. 1987 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Photocopy. 25 pages. -- Author: Murray, Robin.
  - "Struggle in the Market.", June 9, 1905 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Photocopy. 1 page. -- Author: Metcalf, David.
  - Metro Cammell and Metro Cammell Weymann Joint Shop Stewards Committee. Metro Cammell: A Victim of Government Transport Policy. (Box 6, Folder 26)
    Original Bound Publication. 22 pages.
  - "More Light in the North." The Economist., Apr. 1987 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    Original Journal. 3 pages.